Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection
1868-1997
PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
1000000.0 Linear feet
- City College of New York - New York, NY
  - Main building - details of lower part of main tower with entrances, ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384)
  - Main building - detail of sides of assembly hall, ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384)
  - Main building - interior details of assembly hall, ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384)
  - Main building - section of assembly hall showing proscenium arch etc., ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384)
  - Main building - details of wing E, ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384)
  - Main building - details of curved wings B and D, ink and linen (damaged) (Box 384)
  - Main building - section with details of platform end of assembly hall, ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384)
  - Main building - terrace elevation, ink on linen (damaged), 1903-1-26 (Box 384)
  - Main building - campus, Convent Ave. & park elevations, ink on linen (damaged), 1903-1-26 (Box 384)
  - Main building - side elevation, ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - details of building and stack, ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384)
  - Main building - details of tracery windows assembly hall, ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - interior details of north and south towers, 1905-2-20 (Box 384-A)
  - All buildings - general detail of windows, ink on linen (Box 384-A)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - interior details of central portion of building, ink on linen (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - alterations of openings in walls of north and south towers and omissions of part of 5th floor in north tower, ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - layout of soffit in proscenium arch, ink on linen, 1907-1-29 (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - platform end of assembly hall, ink on linen (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - details of upper part of south tower, ink on linen (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - diagrams of openings in south and east walls of north tower, ink on linen, 1905-10-26 (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - detail of sides of assembly hall, graphite on trace, 1904-1-21 (Box 384-A)
  - Dimensions of rough openings in organ chamber at clerestory level, graphite on trace, 1906-4-6 (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - detail of terra cotta work, ink on linen, 1904-7-5 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - plan of plinths of entrance and vestibule doors, graphite on trace, 1905-9-19 (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - additional windows - campus elevation wing E, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - details for changes in toilet rooms, graphite on trace, 1907-7-5 (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - organ fronts, ink on linen, 1906-3-14 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - openings and doors showing lintels and bucks, ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 384-A)
  - Main building - elevator and book lift enclosure in stack room and reading room, ink on linen, 1906-4-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - entrance floor plan, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - running track floor plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-10-24 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - basement floor plan, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - sections a-a & b-b, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - entrance floor plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - foundation plan, ink on linen, 1903-1-26 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - main floor plan, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - roof plan, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - roof plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - cellar floor plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - running track floor plan electric work, ink on linen (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - plan of running track, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - main floor plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - cellar floor plan, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - mezzanine floor plan, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - 138th Street elevation, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - section c-c, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - end elevations, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - mezzanine floor plan, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - mezzanine floor plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - campus elevation, ink on linen, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-A)
  - Gymnasium - swimming pool floor plan electric work, ink on linen, 1905-7-25 (Box 384-A)
  - Sub-freshman building - detail of courts on Amsterdam Ave., ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Sub-freshman building - details of 138th St., 139th St., and campus elevations, ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Sub-freshman building - interior details except assembly hall, ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Sub-freshman building - details of central & side towers - campus elevation; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-4 (Box 384-B)
  - Sub-freshman building - interior details of assembly hall; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Sub-freshman building - detail of central pavilion Amsterdam Ave.; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Gymnasium - interior details; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Gymnasium - details of building; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-B)
  - Main building - details of ends of assembly hall; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - interior details, main corridor - ground and 1st floors; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - parabolic screen and construction of proscenium arch; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - sections; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-1 (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - overhead work for reading room elevator; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - column schedule (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - details of staircase and elevator back of paraboloid, 1904-11-1 (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - strain sheets; ink on linen (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - assembly hall details; ink on linen (Box 384-C)
  - Main building - detail of furring, metal lathing to arches of organ chamber toward aisles; ink on linen (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - structural details, ink on linen (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - details of construction of running track; ink on linen (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - cast iron door frames and partitions from stairs; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - layout of floor numbers exercise room; ink on linen, 1907-4-1 (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - bronze eyelets for swimming bath; graphite on trace, 1905-5-18 (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - finish of window stools in east and west toilets, mezzanine fl.; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-11-14 (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - brick arch in campus entrance; graphite on trace, 1904-6-4 (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - interior doors, trim, etc - mezzanine, main, & running track floors; graphite on trace, 1905-7-10 (Box 384-C)
  - Gymnasium - additional showers in the tank room; graphite on trace, 1907-7-5 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - detail of finish in bag punching room; ink on linen (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - plan showing cement floor tiling; graphite on trace, 1906-8-10 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - interior doors and trim, basement and entrance floors; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-9-15 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - entrance doors on campus; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-7-27 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - pilaster cap, top of enameled brick columns around swimming pool; graphite on trace, 1905-10-18 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - slate copings, steps, and platforms around swimming pool; graphite on trace (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - metal covered doors; graphite on trace, 1905-10-13 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - cast bronze overflow gutter for swimming pool; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-6-4 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - cast bronze overflow gutter for swimming pool; graphite on trace, 1906-12-6 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - slop sink doors on main and running track floors; graphite on trace, 1905-7-26 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - revised detail for steps into swimming pool; graphite on trace, 1906-6-1 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - wood screen under stairs on entrance floor & small double screen on stair landing above; graphite on trace (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - iron bucks and lintel for vestibule doors, campus entrance; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-1-6 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - revised plan of locker rooms; graphite on trace (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - diagram for setting tile around swimming pool; graphite on trace, 1905-10-10 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - mezzanine floor, detail of tool case in corridor; graphite on trace (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - plan of kitchen, mezzanine floor; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-10-24 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - inside elevation of doorway; graphite on trace (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - doors and windows in hand ball courts, doors in subway entrance in campus, door to closet in corridor entrance floor, mutin in transomover doorsin corridor campus entrance; graphite on trace, 1905-7-19 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - change in base, campus entrance; graphite on trace, 1904-7-18 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - diagram showing placing of figures in cornice; graphite on trace, 1904-4-19 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium & Mechanical Arts buildings - stepping shelf for lockers, 1906-3-21 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - plan and elevation of swimming pool spring board, 1906-8-27 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - new slate curb in front of showers; graphite on trace, 1907-10-4 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - openings to steam cocks, basement running and track floors; ink on linen, 1905-1-14 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - letters for directory schedule & bulletin board; graphite on trace, 1906-11-2 (Box 232)
  - Chemical Building - details of entrance btwn piers A and A1; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - interior details; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - detail of cast iron door frames and partitions from stairs, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - system of drainage; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - roof trusses; ink on linen (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - campus elevation revised; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - end elevations revised; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - schedule for steel columns and cast iron bases; ink on linen (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - geometrical progression of risers in lecture room; ink on linen (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - strain diagram for lattice girders in attic; ink on linen, 1904-12-30 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - sliding door in room #2, 2nd floor; graphite on trace, 1906-5-5 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - first floor, details for wood-work; graphite on trace, 1906-5-4 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - relation of skylight to ridge roll, over assembly hall; graphite on trace, 1906-8-24 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - spacing of angle irons for end wing skylights; graphite on trace, 1906-6-19 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - diagram of existing condition of plumbing; graphite on trace, 1905-10-18 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - new tile connection, ground floor room #4; ink on linen, 1905-3-24 (Box 372)
  - Gymnasium - B, D, & E tier girders; ink on linen, 1904-6-8 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - framing: roof plan; ink on linen, 1904-7-21 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - duct loft floor beams and bottom chord bracing of trusses; ink on linen, 1904-4-18 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - framing plan: "E" tier or running track floor; ink on linen, 1904-4-14 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - framing: "D" tier or main floor plan; ink on linen, 1904-4-6 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - framing: "C" tier or mezzanine floor plan; ink on linen, 1904-4-4 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - framing: "B" tier or entrance floor plan; ink on linen, 1904-3-31 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - column setting plan and A tier of beams; ink on linen, 1904-3-24 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - lintels, door bucks and anchors, 1905-3-2 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - bracing for trusses; ink on linen, 1904-4-13 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - roof purlin plan; ink on linen, 1904-4-21 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - detail of turrets; ink on linen, 1904-4-25 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - trusses T4; ink on linen, 1904-4-15 (Box 232)
  - Gymnasium - trusses T1, T2 & T3; ink on linen, 1904-4-12 (Box 232)
  - Chemical Building - cross section of roof above wings, section thro' ventilator, etc.; ink on linen (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - cross section of roof above centre portion of bldg; ink on linen, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - framing for bay window, 1905-2-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - battlements around ornamental panels, campus elevation; ink on linen, 1905-1-4 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - transom over doors at entrance on Convent Ave.; ink on linen, 1907-12-11 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - pipe chase at piers A & A1, 1906-3-21 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - doors from halls to room #9, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-7-6 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - entrance door, west elevation; graphite on trace, 1906-9-10 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - sidewalk lift on 140th St.; graphite on trace, 1907-8-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - lecture hall, detail of curve in ceiling; graphite on trace, 1906-12-12 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - interior doors; graphite on trace (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - iron stairway and balcony, room #5 1st floor; graphite on trace, 1906-4-27 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - diagram showing additions and omissions in tile work, 2 sheets; graphite on trace (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - cast iron door frame btwn room #2 & stair hall, 2nd floor, 1906-6-20 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - details for area copings, 1906-12-21 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - two brick arches in central entrance, 1904-6-4 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - ridge rolls; graphite on trace, 1906-8-17 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - revised two brick arches to openings in Convent Ave entrance; graphite on trace, 1904-9-9 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - two brick arches to openings in Convent Ave entrance; graphite on trace, 1904-6-4 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - iron bucks and lintels for interior doors, etc.; graphite on trace, 1905-1-18 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - valves for controlling supplies to laboratories; graphite on trace, 1906-5-9 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - position of interior windows & finish of stool & blackboard; graphite on trace, 1906-7-2 (Box 372)
  - Chemical & Mechanical Building - ceiling lights under the vault lights on the 140th St sidewalk, 1907-7-24 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - external doors, Convent Ave entrance; graphite on trace, 1906-3-30 (Box 372)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, research lab, room 4, 2nd story; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 13, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 1, 2, 5, 8, 3rd floor; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 1, ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 7, ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 9, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 13, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 1, 6, 9, 17, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, demonstration table, room 9, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, misc. details; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 1 & 12, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 8, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 7, 2nd fl & room 17, ground fl; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 3, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 10, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 11, 2nd fl & room 7, 3rd fl; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 2, 2nd fl; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 1, 6, 9 & 17, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 5, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 8 & 19, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 10, 12, 16, 1st floor; room 8 ground floor; room 9 basement; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 14 & 15, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 4, ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 16 ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 2, ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 5 & 6, ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 14 & 15, ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 1, basement; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, room 3 basement & room 13 ground floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, details of sinks; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, misc details: cocks and hardware; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - electrical work, diagram showing changes in fixtures in museum and museum gallery; graphite on trace, 1906-10-11 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - suggested design of table pedestal if made of metal; graphite on trace, 1908-2-23 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - revised details of hood #63, 2nd fl; graphite on trace, 1907-8-30 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - relative positions of com. air plant, vac. plant, & dis. water plant in basement; graphite on trace, 1906-10-10 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, 1st floor, numbering of laboratory tables & doors to rooms; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, ground floor plan, numbering of laboratory tables & doors to rooms; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, 2nd floor, numbering of laboratory tables & doors to rooms; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, basement, numbering of laboratory tables & doors to rooms; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, 3rd floor plan, numbering of laboratory tables & doors to rooms; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - revised detail of hood in 2nd fl lecture room; graphite on trace, 1907-9-5 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - revised arrangment of sink and shelves on west wall of room 3, basement; graphite on trace, 1907-11-16 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 3 & 4, 2nd floor; graphite on trace, 1906-8-14 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - details of ladders in supply rooms; graphite on trace, 1906-9-13 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 6 & 8, 1st floor; graphite on trace, 1906-7-27 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for room 1, 2nd floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 11 & 12, 2nd floor; graphite on trace, 1906-7-27 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 7 & 8, 2nd floor; graphite on trace, 1906-8-3 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 12, 14 & 15, 1st fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-7-23 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 16, 17 & 19, 1st fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-7-23 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for room 8, 3rd fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-8-14 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout, room 1, 1st fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-7-24 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - thermostats & electric switches, 2nd floor plan; graphite on trace, 1906-6-14 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - thermostats & electric switches, 3rd floor plan; graphite on trace, 1906-6-14 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - vulcanite seat, etc. for pneumatic throughs; graphite on trace, 1906-11-2 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - brick supports under troughs for steam bath C#108; graphite on trace, 1906-8-14 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - details of sidewalk lift on 140th St.; graphite on trace, 1908-1-27 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - offsets for pipe inlets; graphite on trace, 1907-4-16 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - details showing steam return; graphite on trace, 1906-11-12 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - layout of steam lines, ground floor; graphite on trace, 1903-8-3 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for rooms 8, 9 & 10, 1st floor; graphite on trace, 1906-7-23 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for room 13, 1st floor; graphite on trace, 1906-7-23 (Box 373-A)
  - Chemical Building - details for alberene shelves and iron brackets for generators; graphite on trace, 1907-3-22 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, rooms 1, 6, 9 & 17, 1st floor; graphite on trace (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - furniture & equipment, ground floor room 11; graphite on trace (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - layout of new high pressure vacuum system; graphite on trace (damaged, 2 pieces) (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - closets for transformers & rheostat motors & fans, rm 2, 2nd fl; graphite on trace, 1907-8-3 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - revised position of cradle for distilled water tank; graphite on trace, 1906-10-29 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - details showing cases where dimensions at building vary from drawing; graphite on trace, 1907-4-12 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - position of shelf & brackets for spring rollers, 3rd fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-7-6 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - frame for colored glass, room 3, 2nd fl.; graphite on trace, 1908-8-17 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - chart frame in lecture room, 2nd floor; graphite on trace, 1907-4-16 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - revised diagram plan of distilled water distribution, attic floor level; graphite on trace, 1906-10-29 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - ground floor plan, location of boxes for pipes; graphite on trace, 1906-1-17 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - 3rd floor plan, location of boxes for pipes; graphite on trace, 1906-1-22 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for room 10, 2nd floor; graphite on trace, 1906-8-23 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - 2nd floor, showing location of boxes for pipes; graphite on trace, 1906-1-22 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - pipe layout for lecture room, 2nd fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-8-23 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - pipe level layout; graphite on trace, 1906-8-16 (Box 373-B)
  - Chemical Building - paneled jambs for doors to all small rooms; graphite on trace, 1906-7-6 (Box 373-B)